A Guide to the Ford Foundation records, Office of the Vice President, Office Files of David Bell FA624
Rockefeller Archive Center
- Appendix A: Reports Accessioned
  - Ford Foundation/ID. Summary tables -- FY 1974 and earlier years, 1975 May 19 (Report 2273)
  - Ford Foundation/ID Summary tables -- FY 1975 and earlier years, 1976 April 26 (Report 8977)
  - Ford Foundation/ID. Summary tables -- FY 1976 and earlier years, 1977 February 23 (Report 8978)
  - Ford Foundation/ID. Summary tables -- FY 1977 and earlier years, 1978 March 16 (Report 6498)
  - Ford Foundation/ID. Summary tables -- FY 1978 and earlier years, 1979 May 18 (Report 6497)
  - Ford Foundation/ID. Summary tables -- FY 1979 and earlier years, 1980 May 28 (Report 8976)
  - Ford Foundation. Support of International Studies in American universities, 1969 March (Report 1355)
  - Kerwin, Robert W. Support of education for business and industrial development in the international program of the Ford Foundation, 1967 January (Report 3620)
  - Nelson, Courtney A. Syria, 1976 April (Report 8906)
  - Heaps, David. Taiwan, 1973 September (Report 8970)
  - Hourani, Albert H. Thoughts on the political environment in the Middle East and North Africa, 1972 February (Report 1981)
  - King, Richard G. Thoughts on the role of evaluation in the Ford Foundation Latin American program, 1967 August (Report 2703)
  - Sutton, F. X. Tolerable rates of economic development and social change, 1966 (Report 3062)
  - Kingsley, J. Donald. Treatment of Jewish minorities in Arab countries since June 1967 with particular attention to the UAR, 1968 January (Report 8904)
  - Lewis, Stephen R. Jr. Trip report Middle East, January 25 through February 8, 1975, 1975 February (Report 9188)
  - Rabb, Harriet. Trip to Africa for the Foundation (April 25 through May 17, 1980), 1980 June (Report 8972)
  - Ruof, Peter. Trip to Europe, European Institute for Policy Research, 1972 March (Report 9049)
  - Brimmer, Andrew. (Trip to Southern Africa and the Middle East), 1975 November (Report 8985)
  - (Marshall, Dorothy). (Trip to West Africa, East Africa, and India), 1974 November (Report 8973)
  - Cleaves, Peter. The United Nations University: an institutional profile, 1975 November (Report 8971)
  - Bell, David E. U.N. University meeting on "Human and social development", Tokyo, November 10-14, 1975, 1975 December (Report 2879)
  - Lowenthal, Abraham F. U.S.-Mexican relations, 1980 October (Report 8951)
  - Ward, F. Champion. Understandings respecting future support of educational development, 1975 December (Report 9015)
  - Ford Foundation. University programs of training and research in public policy, 1972 December (Report 2448)
  - Ford Foundation. Unofficial record of conference of overseas representatives and home office, Feb. 25 - March 3, 1954 (Report 3039)
  - Henderson, Vivian W. Untitled letter to Haskell Ward re: trip to Africa, 1975 January (Report 9189)
  - Bell, David E. Untitled letter to Patricia M. Wald re: Affirmative Action in the International Division, 1974 September (Report 7878)
  - Bundy, McGeorge. Untitled letter to Senator Vance Hartke re: the financial status of the Ford Foundation, 1974 November (Report 9202)
  - Brimmer, Andrew. Untitled report on trip to Southern Africa and the Middle East on behalf of the Foundation, 1975 November (Report 8965)
  - Hayes, F. O. et al. The Urban Institute, 1968 - 1978: an evaluation of its performance, prospects and financial problems, 1978 June (Report 3743)
  - Harrison, Gordon. Visit to Beirut, 1972 April (Report 8851)
  - Goodwin, Craufurd D. Visit to Beirut and Cairo field offices, 1974 May (Report 9046)
  - Bell, David E. Visit to China, Sept. 2-16, 1979, 1979 September (Report 7036)
  - Ward, F. C. Visit to India, Dacca, Bangkok, Indonesia, February 25, 1977 - April 8, 1977 (Report 7920)
  - (Robin, John P.) Visit to Mogadishu by Messrs. Robin and Anderson, Friday 30th August to Tuesday, 3rd September, 1968 October (Report 8913)
  - Goodwin, Craufurd D. Visit to Poland and the USSR: May 9-24, 1971, 1971 June (Report 4697)
  - Nelson, Courtney A. Visit to R1yadh, 1974 February (Report 8894)
  - Bell, David E. Visit to the Middle East, February 23 - March 8, 1969, 1969 March (Report 1385)
  - Ford Foundation. Vols. I and II of papers prepared for Pakistan Review held in New York City - September 16 and 17, 1969, 1969 September (Report 2355)
  - Barber, Elinor G. West Africa visit, February 1980, 1980 April (Report 7925)
  - Germain, Adrienne. Women in International Division programming, 1975 January (Report 8949)
  - Barber, Elinor G. Women-related interests at Harvard/MIT, 1980 December (Report 8935)
  - Bell, David E. Work plans between now and March, 1975 December (Report 8996)
  - Hardin, Lowell S. World agriculture and the Ford Foundation, 1979 July (Report 9004)
  - Dye, Richard W. Year-end report, 1971 January (Report 8930)